[ED.
We are Ochanoma.
I am Nanako Kamata.
I am Kanami Ishiguri.
I am Nanami Kumamoto.
Pleased to meet you.
Today, these three of us are here.
We are going to do a red fox udon noodle eating contest.
Yay!
I like udon,
That's right.
Kirara Yonemura likes frozen udon very much.
Kirara once served me frozen udon,
That's when I discovered the taste of udon, and I started eating it often,
I often eat this red fox, too.
Oooh!
But this time, I would like to compare them,
So, this time, we are going to compare the taste of red kitsune in Hokkaido, Eastern Japan, Kansai, and Western Japan,
Have you ever eaten this?
No, I haven't.
No, I have not.
I'm going to choose the Hokkaido version.
I live in Chiba Prefecture.
Yes, I have.
Kanto.
Yes.
I live in Western Japan.
That's right.
Now then. I would like to decide the order of eating,
Which would you like to eat first?
I have heard that udon in Kansai is not very flavorful,
I have heard that people in Kansai are always surprised when they go to Kanto because of the strong taste of udon,
I thought it would be easier to understand if I eat the thin ones first rather than the thick ones,
What do you think about Kansai?
I think it's good.
Yes, I think it's a good idea. So, Kansai is No. 1.
Number one.
What about next?
But in terms of color, if we say it's dark, isn't it like this?
That's for sure.
I think Kansai, Eastern Japan, Hokkaido, and Western Japan are darker in that order.
You want to learn from that?
Let's learn.
Let's try it.
Then, I would like to eat in the order of Kansai, Eastern Japan, Hokkaido, and Western Japan.
Yay!
Yes. Then, I would like to start with Kansai dialect.
Can I open this now?
Yes.
Who wants to open the Kansai?
Go ahead.
As a representative of the food lovers, I guess.
Wow!
That's great. That's in there.
Fried tofu.
Oh!
Abura-age must be right.
Abura-age. It didn't come up now.
What's this?
Peel off the lid halfway and take out the powdered soup.
(1) OK.
②Open the powdered soup over the noodles and pour boiling water up to the inside line.
Pour it in. Wait a minute.
Can either of these go in?
But please add shichimi togarashi (seven spice red pepper) on top of (3) to taste.
Is this shichimi togarashi too?
I can't break it.
Then, what's the trick?
Let's do it! Nana-chan!
I'm going for it.
Nana, you're in charge of cooking for the tea no man.
Oh, that's right. Actually.
Just a little.
OK!
It's done.
Smells good.
Is it hot?
Yes, it is.
It looks so good.
Are you okay?
Safe!
Okay, let's wait for five minutes.
Are we all waiting for five minutes?
No, they don't.
Who's shortening it?
I can't wait.
How long do you want to wait?
If it's 3 minutes, I eat it in 2.5 minutes.
If it's 3 minutes.
Yes, I do.
30 seconds for 30 minutes.
That's right.
Nana!
That's too much!
Thanks for the coffee.
Can you wait?
Do you think I can wait? I do.
I'm a schoolgirl.You know those school bagged noodles I eat a lot?
I eat those a lot,
Even those, like the 4 1/2 minute ones, I fry them for about 3 1/2 minutes.
But I also fry them a little harder.
I enjoy how they get softer and softer as they get harder and harder.
When I put hot water in, I go into eating mode.
So I put out a different food and wait for 5 minutes while eating it slowly.
I'm a genius.
Then I can eat and be satisfied,
It's just perfect.
It's a great way to eat cup noodles.
I love it.
You eat them all the time.
I love cup noodles.
I can't wait.
I think it's time to go.
If you open it and put chili in it, it'll be time to go.
Let's open it!
OK!
But it's been about 5 seconds now.
Wow! Looks so good!
Are the fried tofu bits popping?
It's flabby! Looks delicious!
Just like Rocco's cheeks.
The Red Fox Udon Kansai version is ready!
We divided the finished product into small portions,
We will eat it like a tasting!
Let's start with the appearance.
But I was impressed earlier when I opened it,
The soup is obviously very thin.
The color is light.
It smells something of the usual delicious smell.
It smells good.
Let's eat together in the tea room.
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Mochi Mochi.
Delicious.
Mochi-mochi.
The same consistent taste as usual.
The eggs are so delicious.
There were exactly three eggs in the package, so the three of us opened one each.
Here it is.
It's like a little sizzle.
It's true. They melt in your mouth.
Delicious.
I think all noodles are delicious in common.
Yes, they are.
The soup stock makes the difference.
It's amazing. I don't know, it doesn't taste close at all.
It's like what I usually eat.
What is it?
I really like this.
It tastes so good.
I wonder what it is.
It's like dashi.
Yes, it is. It's like breakfast dashi.
It has a soft dashi feeling.
It's genius.
It feels like Japanese food.
Yes.
What's in this?
Bonito, kelp, mackerel, surume, and sardine.
Mackerel?
Is it mackerel? Is that why it looks Japanese?
But everything in it is Japanese.
Ah, yes.
It's delicious. This is the taste of light soy sauce.
It's a little bit new for us, but it's very tasty.
Delicious.
Next, I would like to try the eastern part.
Let's eat!
The color of the soy sauce is a little darker than that of the Kansai region.
That's my impression.
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
There was an egg in it earlier, but now there is a fish paste-like substance in it.
I love it!
I'm so happy!
Bon appétit!
I drank the seal, it's really thick.
That was fast.
Really?
Yes, it is.
It's thick.
It's totally different!
It's totally different.
I like all kinds of things, and I eat everything,
I think I don't have a very good tongue,
It's totally different. I can tell.
What?
I was surprised.
But I thought I've had this taste before.
It tastes familiar.
The fish paste is delicious.
What's in it? Bonito?
I think it tastes very much like bonito.
What is this?
What is it called?
It's like a night snack.
It's the kind of thing you eat when you feel a little guilty.The kind of thing you eat when you feel a little guilty.
A little bit of a gusty taste.
It's so good. Red fox udon for a day.
What? I can do it.
Yellow for breakfast. Pink for dinner.
You should try it that way too!
Let's move on!
Yes! Let's go to Hokkaido!
First of all, this is Hokkaido.
The color is even darker.
And it has a slightly transparent orange tinge.
It is transparent.
Now let's eat.
Bon appétit!
The package says that this is a sweet juice,
I love sweet foods.
I will eat it.
Delicious.
Just by eating the noodles, it's different.
It's totally different.
Wait, I think I like this the best.
This is what I usually eat.
It's Hokkaido shishi, right?
Because it went through my mouth without any sense of discomfort.
In a good way, there is no surprise. For me.
It's the taste I usually eat.
It's totally different.
It tastes like, you know, tsuyu.
It's all tsuyu.
It tastes like warming.
It tastes like lunch.
It's lunch.
It's amazing.
You get home from school and you get hungry before dinner is served.
I used to eat rice bowls and such like a snack,
It tastes like that time. It tastes very much like that.
It's true, but I can still taste the sweetness. It's amazing.
I guess Hokkaido.
I know it says "sweetness," but it really is sweet.
It's sweet and very soft on the palate,
The way it goes down your throat is just like in Hokkaido.
What's in this?
Bonito and shredded kelp.
Is the kelp sweet?
Do you know what Shirishiri-Kombu is?
Do you know what rishiri kelp is?
No?
Rishiri is a kind of Hokkaido. It's like this, right here in Hokkaido.
There are two islands attached to Hokkaido called Rishiri Island and Leven Island.
The kelp you can get from Rishiri Island.
The kelp from those islands is sweet.
It's sweet.
I want to go there.
I've always wanted to go to Ririshiri-shima and Leven-jima,
I want to go there someday.
I want to eat there.
I want to go there to eat.
I'm going to go there.
Let's go!
Too much soup!
Yes. Now, let's go to the fourth and last one.
I'd like to try the western Japan version.
The color is the lightest.
The color is like salt ramen.
I thought the color of the soup was very pale in the Kansai version,
It is even lighter than that.
The lower part of the soup is paler.
The higher you go, the darker it gets.
Hokkaido is cold, right?
Because it's cold, the flavor is not absorbed, so the soup becomes thicker and thicker.
I have heard that.
That's why the taste of miso and other things in Hokkaido seem to be thicker.
Sorry if it's a lie.
I'm sorry if it's a lie.
Bon appétit!
It's already refreshing.
I had the Hokkaido version earlier, and it was the most flavorful so far,
I could easily understand the difference between the two,
This one has a very refreshing taste.
Dinner?
It's like a dinner on a diet, isn't it?
I can see why. I think I'm going to lose weight.
Yes, yes.
You can eat without feeling like you're losing money. This one.
The taste is pretty easy to understand.
The calorie count is also on the list.
I like this one the best.
Really?
I've been saying I like them all.
It's so good. Rocco, did you grow up eating this?
It tastes like this.
Nostalgic?
It tastes just like this.
If you eat something from Eastern Japan, you'll feel strange.
It's different from what I used to eat.
On the other hand, from my point of view in Hokkaido, it tastes very refreshing.
I just finished comparing 4 kinds.
They were all delicious.
It was so delicious.
It was a happy time of just eating,
Do you have a favorite name?Does everyone have a preferred name?
Yes, I do.
Then, can we do it on the same day?
Yes, I do!
Kubota and Rocco are in West Japan.
I'm Kansai.
I think I always eat in western Japan,
I was so impressed with the fried tofu on top,
It was delicious.
You live in Eastern Japan, though, Mr. Kubota?
Yes, I do. I live in eastern Japan,
I live in eastern Japan, but the western Japan one has a refreshing taste and sweetness that is better than the eastern one,
It is my type of taste, and I have become a big fan.
I lived in Hokkaido for more than 10 years,
I lived in Hokkaido for more than 10 years, but this was the first time I tasted Kansai's red kisunu,
I was so shocked,
The sweetness is amazing.
And it has a clean taste.
I could feel this.
I felt like I had met a new convenience,
Hokkaido has a strong flavor,
I was used to that, so this was the freshest taste I had ever had,
I was used to that, so this was the freshest taste I had ever tasted,
It was the freshest, so it was a shame.
Everything was delicious.
We are about to release our third single,
We are going to release our third single and have a release event.
We will do it in the summer.
Whenever I go to various regions, I always wonder what souvenirs to buy.
I know.
I'll definitely buy a red fox.
I'm sure of it.
Even if they don't sell this package,
Even if they don't sell this package, I think it tastes different when you buy it and eat it there,
We would love to try it.
Bye bye!